# ZARATE FACUNDO

#### **PORTFOLIO**

https://facundozarate.info

## **GET IN CONTACT**

Home: +54 2613378587

facundo.zarate97@gmail.com

Córdoba 170, Palmira, Mendoza, Argentina

#### PERSONAL PROFILE

Thanks to my specialized training, I believe I can add value and continue to develop professionally in a company that matches my values and expectations.

As a proactive and highly motivated person, I am able to adapt to any circumstance and always give my best in any project, while striving for teamwork and fostering soft skills, as a fundamental source of any work team.

# AREAS OF EXPERTISE

- Hands-on SQL experience
- Java, HTML, JavaScript and PHP experience
- High knowledge in web development frameworks such as Laravel and Livewire.
- Back-end developer for mobile applications in Android Studio

#### **WORK EXPERIENCE**

#### **IT MANAGER**

FyM Servicios | 2020 - Present

- CCTV and computer network project manager
- Directs Web Apps projects
- Advises customers regarding maintenance of software system

#### JUNIOR DEVELOPER

FyM Servicios. | 2018 - 2020

- · Stored, retrieved, and manipulated data
- Designed and built web-based aplications using JavaScript, HTML,CSS and PHP
- Performed user requeriments analysis to increase user satisfaction during rapid application development

## **EDUCATION HISTORY**

#### UTN - UNIVERSIDAD TECNOLÓGICA NACIONAL

Software Engineer, 2017 - Present

• I am currently in my fourth year of my career.